## PHAM DUY MINH

FRONT-END DEVELOPER



### 0333 454 717

### ✓ duyminh081201@gmail.com

- Quân 10, TP Hồ Chí Minh
- in linkedin.com/in/minhdp
- duyminh.dev

## SKILLS

- Frontend Development: HTML,
   CSS, JS, TS, React, Tailwind, Ant
   Design, Redux, Responsive
- Methodologies: Scrum, Agile
- Tools: Figma, Postman, GitHub, GitLab. Jira. Lark
- Others: Data Structures & Algorithms, Problem-Solving, teamwork

## **EDUCATION**

## HO CHI MINH CITY UNIVERSITY OF EDUCATION

Software Engineering

2019 - 2023

GPA: 3.47

## CERTIFICATE

Agile scrum project management

Angular - The Complete Guide

## REWARD

2021-2022

Won the third prize for scientific research students school

## **PROFILE**

I have more than 1 year of experience as a Front-end Developer. I am passionate about creating intuitive and efficient user systems. I enjoy working in a team, am eager to learn, and am open to new technologies. I am looking for another opportunity in a new environment and look forward to collaborating and growing with your team.

## EXPERIENCE

### **SUPERSHIP**

Front-end Developer

10/2023 - Present

SuperShip provides logistics services including domestic freight transportation, COD payment management, order tracking, and supply chain management, helping optimize the delivery process and supporting e-commerce businesses. And systems related management such as: SuperShip, SuperAl and mini app on Zalo platform.

Use React, Tailwind CSS, and Ant design, etc...

- Building and structuring the entire front-end source code
- Integrate commitlint, eslint, and lint-staged into source code
- Developing reusable components for the system
- Developing and implementing new front-end features
- Implementing responsive design
- Integrating APIs into the website
- Maintaining and refactoring code
- Fixing website issues and bugs as they arise

### Mini App

- Use React, Tailwind CSS, and ZaUI to develop a mini app on the Zalo platform.
- Integrate Zalo platform-specific APIs for mini apps.

### **Portal**

Use Tailwind, HTML, CSS, JS, Sergey to implement the interface and integrate the API

### SuperShip Dashboard

Developed a web application with separate mobile and desktop sources, dynamically rendering different UIs based on screen size. Configured both versions to securely share authentication tokens, ensuring seamless user experience across platforms.

# PHAM DUY MINH

FRONT-END DEVELOPER



### **1** 0333 454 717

### duyminh081201@gmail.com

- Quận 10, TP Hồ Chí Minh
- in linkedin.com/in/minhdp
- duyminh.dev

## SKILLS

- Frontend Development: HTML,
   CSS, JS, TS, React, Tailwind, Ant
   Design, Redux, Responsive
- Methodologies: Scrum, Agile
- Tools: Figma, Postman, GitHub,
   GitLab. Jira. Lark
- Others: Data Structures & Algorithms, Problem-Solving, teamwork

## EDUCATION

HO CHI MINH CITY UNIVERSITY OF EDUCATION

Software Engineering

2019 - 2023

GPA: 3.47

## CERTIFICATE

Agile scrum project management

Angular - The Complete Guide

## REWARD

2021-2022

Won the third prize for scientific research students school

## **PROFILE**

I have more than 1 year of experience as a Front-end Developer. I am passionate about creating intuitive and efficient user systems. I enjoy working in a team, am eager to learn, and am open to new technologies. I am looking for another opportunity in a new environment and look forward to collaborating and growing with your team.

## EXPERIENCE

### TMA SOLUTION

Front-end Internship

3/2023 - 5/2023

- Build websites according to mentor's request using Angular and Tailwind CSS
- Fix errors related to website interface and features
- Make daily work progress reports

#### **EDUPLAX**

10/2022 - 1/2023

### Front-end Internship

- Use ReactJS to build Eduplax's educational products
- Implement websites design from Figma
- Implement responsive websites to suit many devices.
- Integrating APIs into the website
- Developing reusable components for the system
- Fix errors related to website interface and features